Here's the code for the Refresh button in
这里是刷新按钮的代码，在
the forecastfragment menu XML file. We want it to
forecastfragment 菜单的XML文件的部分。我们想要它
appear in the overflow menu, so we set showAsAction
出现在浮动菜单上，所以我们把它的showAsAction属性设置
as never. We also declare the string. You can
成为永不。我们这里也声明了一个字符串。你可以
find the string here in the strings.xml file, which
在string.xml里面找到这个字符串，这个文件
is located in the values folder, which is in
存放在values文件夹里面，res目录的下面。
the res folder. You can get your strings.xml file
你可以把你的string.xml文件里面的字符翻译
translated into different languages. This adds additional values folders,
成为不同的语言。这样添加额外的values文件夹在res下面，
under Res. For example, you would have
比如，你可以这样添加
values-es, for Spanish, values-fr for French. And
values-es，这是西班牙语，values-fr，这是法语。然后
within each of those values folders, you
在每一个values文件夹里面，你
would have a strings.xml file, which would
要有一个strings.xml文件，这个文件里面
contain the localized strings for that language.
包含的是为此类语言所本地化的字符串（也就是翻译过的字符串），
Since translation does cost money, as a
由于翻译有时候是花钱的，给你一个专业的
pro tip, you can mark strings that
提示，你可以把那些
you don't need translated using translatable=false. For example,
你不想翻译的字符串标记为translatable=false。如这样，
if it's a proper name or if it's for debugging like this one,
当这只是一个确定的名字，或者是为了调试存在的，
then you can indicate to the translator that they can skip over this strings
那你可以告诉你的翻译员，说它们可以忽略这些字符串。